The world, what a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
seize it, raise your flag and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless everlasting
world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion I believe.
Someday, somewhere, I'll finally see.
The light I have searched for everywhere.
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart. I know.
A brand new world
that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
A great, long blue sky.
Wearing in the troubled ways.
From all despair I can be saved.
For the horizon on the other side is.
And though I travel far
from where my search began.
Over streets of green and shores of sand.
Through the endless
everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Someday somewhere I'll finally see the
light I will search for everywhere.
I've got to save him.
I've just got to save him.
Judgment has been made.
Now you're nothing.
Can't even defeat a priest like me.
I'll save you!
Ignorant little creature, you're
diving into your own watery grave.
And now for the Sky Knight's noble steed.
You no longer have a purpose.
Follow your master.
I do wish that I could be there to
watch the life drain from your faces.
But alas I have other matters
to attend to
I
wonder if the
three fugitives have been
captured yet could a well really
be that interesting yes don't
you think it's odd that a well
would be stuck under a tree the
balance between civilization
Well, unless we find a way to cross this
Cloud River, we'll be stuck in this forest.
And we're still nowhere
near where we want to be.
It's like the people who built this didn't
know the tree would grow to be so large.
I've never seen anything like it.
Hey, Nami!
Can you see anything up there?!
The island where God lives.
Upper Yard.
Nami!
Say something, would you?
What do you see?
Hey, can you hear me?
What do you think she sees up there?
This island can't be...
There's no way you can win!
After all, I'm a priest,
and you all look so tired.
Why don't you just end this now and die?
My heart can't take any more of this.
Too many surprises.
How it hurts.
You'll be out of options quite soon.
It's sad, really.
Your little boat has nearly
reached the forest's exit,
and when that happens,
it's all over for you.
You'll have nowhere to go unless of
course you suddenly learn to fly!
You'll wander around in this terribly
unfamiliar forest and die of exhaustion!
That won't...
Help me!
Nice try!
My turn now!
Here, dragon attack!
You know you can't run forever.
And wherever you stop, the firebomb
ball will be waiting to incinerate you!
Good.
Looks like we can still make it.
I'll just leave things
here with you, Luffy.
That tree will not give you any shelter.
It's like he's reading my mind.
Stay out of my head and quit following me!
What are you doing?
A wire! What the...
Wait, this must be how
he controls the dragon.
I'll just... No, stop!
Do this!
You ruined my sphere dragon,
you impudent little brat!
Now you die!
Get over here in this instant!
Let go of the dragon, you fool!
There it is.
Yeah, I was right.
I knew I could find the
way out of this place.
Of course, this makes perfect sense.
Why didn't I think of this sooner?
When we fell before, it was
from a very high altitude.
So it's only natural that the
exit be at the same height.
And now that I know where the exit is,
The boat doesn't really matter anymore.
All right, that huge explosion worries me.
I'd better hurry gain time
That was close that maniac must have
had a death wish this isn't good
I've got to intensify my training.
I can't let a weakling like him
get the upper hand in a fight
That might block me from
using my mantra. You're right.
That was close.
It's you.
How are you still alive?
Get off me.
I said let's go.
Do not let him go, Luffy.
You too.
Hey, Sanji, where have you been?
I was out cold on the forest floor.
Where else would I have been, you idiot?
But that's beside the point.
see the point is that you keep
saying challenge this and challenge
that which normally wouldn't
interest me however there are two
helpless ladies waiting for me to
come to their rescue and i refuse
to let them down so i'm proposing
this and i think you'll like it
ordeal of love this guy's an idiot too
unhead me this instant you maggot
It's just not fair!
You have no honor, Jaggy!
You have two against one!
We have no honor?
You creeps kidnapped our friends and
tried to murder a beautiful young angel.
And you accuse us of not having any honor.
I'm good thinking.
It's pretty amazing that you
can predict our movements.
But what good is that?
If you can't do anything to avoid them.
Huh?
Ah!
Stop!
Stop, I said!
Are you listening?
How dare you disobey me?
I'm a priest in God's service,
not being judged by me as a
first-degree crime in Skypiea.
Let me go!
Now listen here.
Attacking me means you declare
war of the almighty God, Ederu!
I got a question.
Do you ever cook?
Well, you don't have to be a chef to
know which dish is best served cold.
You know, this dish is
really quite simple.
Step one, season the main course
with a smattering of defeat.
Then you must brutally and without
hesitation tenderize the meat.
No, you can't do this, no!
No, please, no, don't hurt me!
Delicious!
So Gunfall, the former god, made
his way into the Upper Yard alone.
What's the matter, Isa?
Two voices.
They're gone.
What did you say?
Huh?
You're Mantara?
Yes.
It just happened.
You're saying that you heard two voices,
and then they disappeared suddenly?
You need to be honest with me.
Is this true?
I assume that's yes.
We should believe her.
Ever since she was born,
she's been able to use her
ability of mantra to sense people,
even those who are far away from her.
There's no mistaking her gift.
You sure you don't hear them?
They're not there anymore?
Yeah, I think it stopped.
But it seemed like Gonfall was
fighting a priest and they...
Killed each other?
Nicely done, old man.
There are only three left now.
Which is good for us.
I guess Heaven's actually
answered our prayers.
It's time for us to crush
those priests once and for all.
Yeah!
On your feet!
We're launching a full-scale
attack on the upper yard.
Wifer still makes you nervous, doesn't he?
You have to grow up sooner or later.
Lucky, wait, please!
What is it?
It wasn't Gonefall who
defeated that priest!
There are others on that side of the
island and they're the ones that did
it other people you mean the ones who
entered Skypiea from the Blue Sea?
I don't know who but
they're really scary to me.
So be careful!
I'll try.
Now be a good girl and hand over your bag?
No, I can't this is my special secret bag.
It has treasure in it.
I know that
And it will have even more inside
when I bring it back. Yeah? Yeah.
What's going on?
I'm alive.
What happened?
Second!
Hey, Doc!
Oh, wait, that's me!
He's alive! That's good.
This makes no sense.
I jumped in after him.
I figured we'd sink to our deaths.
I wonder who could have
pulled us out of there.
Hey, what was that?
Hello?
Is someone there?
Ah! Jio!
Ah!
Enough with the mystery, Nami.
Spit it out!
Tell us what you saw!
Quit ordering me around
and just do what I say!
We have to get to the seashore!
Ah!
Would one of you please help me?
You're the leader.
Why don't you help
yourself the seashore? Yes.
It's the only way we can get close
enough to check this thing out
Because to be honest, I won't believe
what I saw until I see it up close.
He couldn't have shut up any sooner!
Guys
Luffy Sanji, I found the
boat, but you gotta move.
I'm serious if we don't
get to it right now
We're gonna be stuck on
this stinking island.
I guess Usopp's okay He's
yelling something about the boat.
Kick it into gear!
The boat's leaving this place
and we gotta get on it now!
Get up here!
You just hold on to my body!
Your what? Here goes!
Usopp!
Now that's what I call marksmanship!
Usopp, you're my hero!
Do you try to kill all
your heroes like that?
I don't think so.
I'm surprised you pulled this off.
Yeah?
Well, no more underestimating me.
That hurt so bad.
I will never let you forget this.
You know, I could have stretched
my arm and grabbed the boat.
Look, we're out of the
boat and out of the forest.
That's all that matters.
Satri has fallen.
Losing control over his mantra only
shows his inexperience with it.
It seems the intruders this time are from
the Blue Sea, but they behave strangely.
The sacrifices are now
moving around freely as well.
However, even if we leave them alone,
they won't find their way off this island.
More importantly...
Do you hear the voice of
a sorrowful warrior, Holy?
It doesn't matter how many times we walk
this road, things always end the same.
Shoulda defeated Gonfall, but
the ordeal of Spheres was broken.
That's where luck will end
for our new challengers.
For them to attempt to see God
is insolence at its greatest.
And their punishment at
my hands will have things
a bit unsettled this
evening in the Upper Yard.
No one here gets out alive.
The ones who escaped
sacrifice are off my list.
It seems there are others roaming
around who are more worthy of my anger!
All of you, listen up!
Today we catch up her yard
at her most vulnerable.
This is the opportunity of a lifetime.
We move full speed ahead and don't
stop until we reach God's shrine.
And do not fear Anaru.
The great warrior Kalgar
is our one and only savior.
Only to him are we true.
Abraham?
Ready. Kamakiri!
Jinbe!
Lucky!
Right!
Be careful!
We split up here!
We vow to the great warrior Kaldura
to light the fire of Shandora!
So the Shandians have come for a fight!
Speaks for itself pretty well.
Look at it.
It's almost unreal.
But it's no fairy tale.
That doesn't make any sense.
Why would this be here?
It looks exactly the same.
It's like a copy.
But it's not.
How do you figure?
This is the other half of
what we saw before. Go on.
It's bugged me for a while.
Why is it that we walk on soil
here instead of Island Cloud?
This dirt,
there's nothing in the makeup of the White
White Sea that would
allow for its existence.
So, the ground that we're walking
on shouldn't exist up here.
Upper Yard was originally on the ground.
I knew that house was off
when I saw it. Thing is,
it's a Twister house, and there was no
staircase leading up to the second story.
And what would make you build
a house on the edge of a cliff?
But then again, it wasn't a cliff at all.
Look closer, it's really unattractive.
the guys gotta have some serious
guts to build a house that ugly!
This is the half of the
island that was ripped away?
This island used to be part of Jaya.
So what that means is a
few hundred years back?
The island below us split in half,
and one side of it rose into the sky.
No!
Either of you know how
that could have happened?
There were south birds,
a whole flock of them.
They're huge.
I didn't know they got so big.
Saru, would you wake up already? Huh?
You're a dead man.
That's the best!
This is no time for goofing off!
The city of gold that
Nolan discovered on the
ground didn't sink into
the ocean like he guessed.
This part of Jaya, it's been
floating in the sky for 400 years!